boris-epshteyn' },
      { name: 'Evan Corcoran', relationship: 'Defense attorney in classified documents case', href: '/entities/individuals/evan-corcoran' },
      { name: 'Lin Wood', relationship: 'Attorney and political ally', href: '/entities/individuals/lin-wood' }
    ],
    controversies: [
      'EPSTEIN COMPLICITY: Documented visits to Epstein properties (Mar-a-Lago, NYC mansion), flight on "Lolita Express" (1993), public praise as "terrific guy" who "likes beautiful women... on the younger side" (2002), association spanning 15+ years, involvement with trafficking network targeting minors',
      'SEXUAL ASSAULT ALLEGATIONS: 26+ women have accused Trump of sexual misconduct including rape allegations by multiple victims, Katie Johnson lawsuit alleging rape at age 13 at Epstein party (1994), Access Hollywood tape admitting to grabbing women "by the pussy", pattern of assault spanning decades',
      'January 6 Insurrection: Incitement of Capitol attack resulting in 5 deaths, 140+ police injuries, $2 billion in damages, 1000+ participants charged',
      'Election Interference: 200+ false claims about 2020 election, coordination with Russians per Mueller Report (145 contacts, 12 indicted officers), Georgia call to "find 11,780 votes"',
      'Classified Documents: Storage of 15 boxes of classified materials at Mar-a-Lago accessible to unauthorized personnel including foreign nationals',
      'Ukraine Extortion: Withholding $391 million in military aid for political investigations (first impeachment)',
      'Tax Evasion: Over $100 million in evaded taxes through offshore structures per Panama Papers and IRS audits',
      'Business Fraud: $25 million Trump University settlement, New York civil fraud judgment of $454 million, 34 felony convictions',
      'Family Separation Policy: Zero-tolerance immigration policy resulting in 5,000+ children separated, deaths, psychological trauma, forced sterilizations',
      'Muslim Ban: Executive orders affecting millions from Muslim-majority countries',
      'Money Laundering: $2 billion Deutsche Bank financing tied to Russian oligarchs, $1 trillion+ in illicit flows',
      'Hush Money: $130,000 to Stormy Daniels, $150,000 to Karen McDougal, campaign finance violations (34 felony convictions)',
      'Georgia RICO: Call to overturn election, fake electors scheme, 13 co-defendants',
      'Obstruction of Justice: Firing FBI Director Comey, witness tampering, 10 instances per Mueller Report',
      'Emoluments Violations: $10+ million from foreign governments through hotels',
      'Pardons for Allies: Pardons of Manafort, Stone, Flynn, Bannon to prevent testimony',
      'Climate Sabotage: Paris Agreement withdrawal, EPA rollbacks, $10 billion fossil fuel ties, contributing to 1 million+ deaths',
      'COVID-19 Crimes: Downplaying pandemic, promoting unproven treatments, 500,000+ preventable deaths',
      'War Profiteering: $110 billion Saudi arms deal enabling Yemen genocide (400,000+ deaths, 8
